carnation.in 2013-04-04

# 

 ** PRIVACY POLICY- CARNATION**

Last modified: November, 2011.

This Privacy Policy applies to all of the products, services and websites offered by Carnation Auto India Pvt. Ltd. (hereinafter referred to as “Carnation”) or its subsidiaries or affiliated companies. By visiting this website you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree please do not use or access our Site. This Privacy Policy describes the information, as part of the normal operation of our services; we collect from you and how we utilize the same. 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us through the details given in the contact us section of our website www.carnation.in (the “Site”).

 **Information we collect and how we use it**

In general, you can visit and surf the Site without disclosing your identity or revealing any personal information about yourself. However, based on your use and activation of certain services we may collect the following types of information:

    * **Information you provide** – To fully use our Site, you will need to register using our online registration form, where you may be required to provide us with your contact and identity information and other personal information as indicated on the forms throughout the Site. You always have the option to not provide information by choosing not to use a particular service or feature on the Site. Our primary goal in doing so is to provide a safe, efficient, smooth and customized experience. This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs, and to customize our Site to make your experience safer and easier. Importantly, we only collect personal information about you that we consider necessary for achieving this purpose.

    * **Information we track** \- We may automatically track certain information about you based upon your behaviour on our site. We use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavioural and search patterns to better understand, protect and serve our users. This information is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on our site or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on our site or not), your computer browser information, and your IP address.

    * **Log information** – When you access the Site via a browser, application or other client our servers automatically record certain information. These server logs may include information such as your web request, your interaction with a service, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser or your account.     

    * **Transactional information** \- If you choose to buy or sell on the Site, we collect information about your buying and selling behaviour. We also collect other users' comments about you in our feedback area.   

    * **Cookies** – When you visit the Site, we send one or more cookies to your computer or other device. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service, including for storing user preferences, improving search results and ad selection, and tracking user trends, such as how people search, analyze our web page flow, measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety. Most cookies are "session cookies," meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may not be able to use or access certain features on the Site which are only available for use via cookies.

    * **User communications** – When you send email or other communications to us, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. When you send and receive SMS messages to or from one of our services that provides SMS functionality, we may collect and maintain information associated with those messages, such as the phone number, the wireless carrier associated with the phone number, the content of the message, and the date and time of the transaction. We may also use your email address to communicate with you about our services. If you choose to post messages on our forum or leave feedback for other users, we will collect that information. We retain this information as necessary to resolve disputes, provide customer support and troubleshoot problems as permitted by law or deemed necessary by us. If other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the Site, we may also collect such information into a file specific to you.  

    * **Third Party Applications** – Carnation may make available third party applications, such as gadgets or extensions, through its services. The information collected by Carnation when you enable a third party application is processed under this Privacy Policy. Information collected by the third party application provider is governed by their own privacy policies.  

    * **Affiliated Services on other sites **– We offer some of our services on or through other web sites. Personal information that you provide to those sites may be sent to us in order to deliver the service. We process such information under this Privacy Policy.

    * ** Other sites** – This Privacy Policy applies to Carnation services only. We do not exercise control over any links or information posted by any other users or third parties, sites that include Carnation applications, products or services, or links from within our various services. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you.

 **Use of Information:** We may use the information we collect to:

    * Provide, maintain, protect, and improve our services (including advertising services) and develop new services;  
    * Protect the rights or property of Carnation or our users;  
    * resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, help promote safe trading, collect fees owed, measure consumer interest in the services provided by us, inform you about online and offline offers, products, services, and updates, customize your experience and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection of the information; and  
    * If you choose to list a car for sale on the Site we use your address and billing information to bill you (if any) and provide associated support.  
    * When a user lists a classified advertisement, and the advertisement receives an expression of interest by the interested user, the interested user will be provided the contact information of the user listing the advertisement as provided in that user's registration form. Similarly when a user expresses an interest in a classified advertisement, the user who has listed the advertisement will be provided the contact information of the interested user as provided in the interested user's registration form.

Apart from the above, you also specifically agree that:

    * We may use personal information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts; and  
    * We may use your personal information to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as targeted banner advertisements, administrative notices, product offerings and communications relevant to your use of the Site.

By accepting the User Agreement and Privacy Policy, you expressly agree to receive this information. If you do not wish to receive these communications, we encourage you to opt out of the receipt of certain communications in your profile. You may make changes to your profile at any time. If we use this information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use.

 **Information sharing**

Carnation only shares personal information with other companies or individuals in the following limited circumstances:

    * We have your consent. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information.  
    * We provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.  
    * We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Carnation, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.

If Carnation becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will ensure the confidentiality of any personal information involved in such transactions and provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

 **Information security**

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, including appropriate encryption and physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.

We restrict access to personal information to Carnation employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to process it on our behalf. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

We may use third parties that we refer to as internal service providers to facilitate or outsource one or more aspects of the business, product and service operations that we provide to you on the Site (e.g., search technology, discussion boards, bill collection, affiliate and rewards programs) and therefore we may provide some of your personal information directly to these internal service providers. These internal service providers' are subject to confidentiality agreements with us and other legal restrictions that prohibit their use of the information we provide them for any other purpose except to facilitate the specific outsourced Site related operation, unless you have explicitly agreed or given your prior permission to them for additional uses.

 **Complaints**

Carnation regularly reviews its compliance with this Privacy Policy. When we receive formal written complaints, it is Carnation’s policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns.

 **Your Consent & Changes to this Privacy Policy**

By using the Site, you consent to the collection and use of the information you disclose on the Site by Carnation. Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and it is your duty to remain up to date with the same.

 **This document is an electronic record in terms of Information Technology Act, 2000 and the amended provisions pertaining to electronic records in various statutes as amended by the Information Technology Act, 2000. This electronic record is generated by a computer system and does not require any physical or digital signatures.**

Carnation.in features information, reviews and advice to buy and maintain new cars in India, used cars, car finance, EMI / Car Price calculators, car exchange and car accessories. Compare car insurance quotes, find & list used cars for sale, car buying /selling guides and also Carnation car service stations or garages that offer quick cars servicing, car repairs, car body shop, for almost all brands, and even a home doorstep car service in over 25 cities... read more about us. All reviews, ranks, ratings & votes on Carnation.in and its associated websites are solely the views & opinions of the users or experts. Carnation.in or CAIPL are not responsible for content on external web sites or partner websites.
